== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ Men. ♪
All right, I have
turned "it" into "ziti,"
Uh, with a triple letter on z
and a double word on the I.
Plus, going down,
I've created "za."
Za?
Uh, a colloquialism for pizza.
One of the five
two-letter words
newly accepted by the National
Scrabble Association.
Unbelievable.
You can call them
if you want.
That's what we
in Scrabble circles call
a two tile takedown.
♪ Bom-bom! ♪
CHARLIE:
Hey, Alan,
is our limo here yet?
Uh, sorry,
I haven't seen a limo.
Oh, 100 points!
♪ Bow-bow! ♪
That's a gorgeous dress,
Courtney.
Thanks. Charlie
insisted on buying it
for me to wear
tonight.
What's the
charity again?
I don't know.
Landmines, orphans.
Landmines for orphans.
I just want
to show you off.
Oh.
Well, you look great.
Thank you.
No, no.
No, there's...
something...
something wrong.
What?
I don't know. I don't know.
Something's...
something's missing.
Oh, I got it.
Ta-dah!
Charlie!
(gasps)
You shouldn't have.
Well, you've done a
lot of things for me
you shouldn't have.
Oh, my...
Now you look great.
God, it is beautiful.
Thank you.
So, what are you
guys up to tonight?
Oh, not much. Just a quiet,
romantic evening at home.
Loser.
Come on, that's not fair.
No, it's my
word-- loser.
Oh. Oh. Oh, uh, well,
then I should point out
that you could have used the C
at the top of the board
and made "closer."
I'll stick with loser.
(phone ringing)
Yeah?
Great. We'll be right out.
Our chariot awaits.
Have fun.
Thanks. You, too.
Do me a favor.
When we get in the limo,
ask the driver
to put up the partition.
You bet.
Isn't that sweet?
She's gonna do more things
she shouldn't.
Gluten-free pretzel?
No, thanks.
Oh, I guess this isn't much
of a Saturday night date.
Alan, it's fine.
I like staying
in with you.
I could probably do
without the ♪ Bom-bom! ♪
Well, I just... I wish
I could take you out
and get you things
like Charlie does.
I don't need those things.
I mean, they're nice.
They're more than nice.
They're what every
girl dreams of.
But let's face it.
Some dreams just
have to die.
Well, I'm-I'm sorry
you had to settle.
I'm not settling.
I'm... I'm accepting.
So you're not rich and
successful like Charlie.
So you can't take
me out in limos
and shower me in diamonds.
So there's no
expensive restaurants
or beautiful dresses.
But?
What?
Well, you know,
I can't take you out,
and I can't give
you stuff, but...
But... I love you?
Why?
Boy, you're just gonna keep
pushing this, aren't you?
No, no. You love me. I'm good.
Let's play Scrabble.
Mm.
Ooh, axolotl!
(laughs)
Uh...
(quietly):
♪ Bom-bom. ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Oh-oh. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 8x11 ♪
Dead From the Waist Down
Original Air Date on December 6, 2010
♪ Men. ♪
Morning.
Pottery Barn?
Yeah, I'm looking for ideas
for a birthday present
for Lyndsey.
At the Pottery Barn?
Well, I don't have your money.
And there are ways
to communicate your feelings
for a woman besides
throwing diamonds at her.
True, but diamonds get you
limo skull.
Pottery Barn won't get you
dry humped
in the back of a city bus.
Charming.
So, uh, how was
the charity soirée last night?
I don't know. We never
made it out of the limo.
Charlie, do you have any idea
how bad you're making me look?
Oh, buddy, that's not me.
That's genetics
and barber school haircuts.
I'm serious. How do you think
it makes me feel
when I'm with Lyndsey,
and I have to watch you
shower Courtney
with limos and diamonds?
Huh. I never thought about that.
I do have a solution, though.
What's that?
Move out.
I-I'm just saying,
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't do so much
of that stuff in front of us.
Again, I have
a solution.
All right, all right, let's just
stipulate for the record
that you want me to move out and
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
What is it you'd have me do?
Not enjoy the money that I earn?
Not lavish it
on the people that I love?
Sneak around in the middle
of the night giving gifts
to my girlfriend, so you don't
get your feelings hurt?
Is that something
you'd consider?
No, but I'll tell you what I will do.
Oh, what's that?
If I should come home some night
to find you standing on a chair
with a rope around your neck
because you can't bear
another moment
of your pathetic life,
I give you my word,
I will kick the chair.
Ooh! Santa Claus bottle stopper.
Only 12 dollars.
I can get her two.
♪ Men. ♪
Dad?
Yeah?
I need money.
Join the club.
Seriously. My clothes
are getting too small.
Jake, I give your mother money
every month
for the express purpose
of buying you whatever you need.
Yeah, well,
that's not how she sees it.
I don't know what
to tell you, buddy.
Things are a little tight
right now.
So are my shoes.
What do you want me to do,
tap into your college fund?
I guess not.
Hang on a second.
Let's not throw that idea out
so quickly.
What do you mean?
Well, realistically,
do you actually see yourself
going to college?
Because if you don't,
we could use that money
to buy you some new clothes,
plus maybe some other things.
You know, it's funny
that you ask that.
I had no interest in college
until a few days ago.
What changed?
I saw this video called
Topless Coeds of the Big Ten,
and I decided
I need to go to college.
You expect me
to pay 30, 40,000 dollars a year
so you can meet drunk girls
who lift their shirts?
Yes, please.
(grunts)
Is that a no
on the clothes money?
I'll talk
to your mother about it.
Oh, now I'm filled
with hope.
CHARLIE:
Hey, Alan,
come here.
Are you gonna
make me feel worse?
Is that even
possible?
I wouldn't think so, but
you usually find a way.
What do you want?
Well, I couldn't help
but overhear you trying
to talk Huckleberry out
of getting an education.
Yeah, not my proudest moment.
But I'm desperate to find a way
to buy Lyndsey a decent
birthday present.
All right,
here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna "lend" you enough so
you can buy her something nice.
How much are we talking about?
Are you kidding?
You're negotiating with me?!
No, no, forget it.
I appreciate the offer, but
I'm not gonna take your money.
I'm-I'm sorry. I think I might
have just had a small stroke.
I thought I heard you say
you're not gonna take my money.
Yeah, you heard me right.
I have to find a way
to buy Lyndsey a nice present
on my own.
It's a matter of self-respect.
Little late for that, isn't it?
If it was for me,
I'd take your money.
If it was for you,
I wouldn't offer it.
But this is my girlfriend.
If I can't do this one thing
for her,
then maybe
I just don't deserve her.
Okay, what's your plan?
I'm not sure,
but when Alan Harper sets
his mind to something,
just stand back
and watch it happen.
Yeah, right.
Cue the theme from Rocky.
(Instrumental intro
for Gonna Fly Now plays)
♪ ♪
♪ Trying hard now ♪
♪ It's so hard now ♪
♪ Trying hard now... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Getting strong now ♪
♪ Won't be long now ♪
♪ Getting strong now... ♪
(Charlie playing
Rocky theme song on piano)
(song ends)
(Alan grumbling)
Need some help?
A little late to ask,
don't you think?
Nope.
(sighs)
Well, the good news is,
I am done.
I have accomplished my mission.
After three weeks
of 16-hour days
at the office and the mall,
I have managed
to earn enough money
to buy Lyndsey
a beautiful birthday present.
Voilà!
A matching set of natural
South Sea Island pearls.
No kidding?
Mm-hmm.
And you got these at the mall?
Uh, well, in the
mall parking lot.
Oh, Alan, you bought pearls
from a guy in a parking lot?
(groans) Not a guy.
A Tahitian wholesaler.
Do you have any idea what the
mark-up is on these things?
By eliminating the middleman,
I saved a fortune.
You sure about that?
Oh, don't worry,
they're real.
I have a certificate
of authenticity.
The word "authenti""
doesn't have a "K" in it.
It's the man's second
language, Charlie.
All right, but for
future reference,
the way you can tell for
sure if pearls are real
is you rub them
on your teeth.
If they're rough,
they're real,
if they're smooth,
they're fake.
Well, fine, fine--
I will prove it to you.
See?
Mmm, rough.
And... oddly minty.
(crunching)
Oh, darn.
♪ Men... ♪
Morning.
Morning. Hey, nice pearls.
Found them in the garbage.
Strange some of the things
people throw away.
I also found what looked like
a half-written suicide note
in your brother's
handwriting.
No kidding?
Should I be worried?
You mean that he won't
go through with it?
He'll be fine-- he's just
having some money problems.
Okay. But fair warning--
he offs himself,
I ain't cleaning it up.
Who's offing themselves?
Nobody.
Nobody important.
Hey, I was wondering,
are you going anywhere today?
Don't try to play me,
knucklehead, just ask.
Can I borrow your car?
No.
Come on.
Dude, that's a very expensive car.
There's no way I'm
putting you behind that wheel.
See you later, Charlie.
I'm going shopping.
Have fun.
JAKE: Courtney,
are you taking
Uncle Charlie's car?
Yeah. Why? I was just thinking
maybe I could drive you.
Save you the hassle
of parking and everything.
Oh, aren't you
the sweetest thing.
Thanks.
See you, handsome!
Yeah, see you, handsome.
Wonderful.
I just got outsmarted
by Mr. Potato Head.
♪ Men... ♪
(football game playing
at low volume)
Hey.
I did a bad
thing, Charlie.
Uh-huh.
A very bad thing.
Sorry to hear it.
I don't even want
to tell you about it.
Good.
I am so ashamed...
Okay, we both know you're gonna
tell me, so just tell me.
Well, in order
to explain it,
I have to go back a few years.
Oh, please, God help me.
Back when Judith and I
were still married
but having problems,
I decided
to try to make her happy
by buying her
a really nice pair
or diamond earrings.
You could afford
diamond earrings?
No alimony,
no child support.
It was a bountiful time.
Uh-huh.
Anyway,
I spent a fortune on them and
I wrapped them up really nice
and took her to
an expensive restaurant
and gave them to her
over cocktails.
And?
She said, "Thanks,"
ordered the lobster,
then filed for divorce.
At which point, I moved in with you.
(sighs)
You're right, Alan,
that was a
very bad thing.
Oh, no, no, that was just the prologue.
Oh, please, God, help me.
So, this afternoon,
I was over at Judith's
to talk to her about using
my child support payments
to buy Jake new clothes.
Yeah?
She's against it.
We argued, she stormed
out of the room
and left me
standing there by myself
in the house I used to own.
Anyway, before I left,
I figured I'd pee.
I didn't really need
to, but, you know,
you got to figure with the
traffic, it's a good defensiv...
Would you please
get to it!
Al-Almost there,
almost there.
So, as I was walking
down the hallway,
I noticed that Judith's
bedroom door was open,
and... I thought about those
beautiful diamond earrings
just sitting there
in her jewelry box
and how I can't even afford
to buy my girlfriend
a birthday present.
Let me guess.
You peed in her
jewelry box.
Judith never even
wore them, Charlie.
You stole diamonds
from your ex-wife?
Yeah.
Kudos!
I don't even know
how it happened.
I mean, it was
like I was in a dream,
and my hands belonged
to someone else.
I have that same
dream all the time.
Except in mine, the hands
do belong to someone else.
I-I'm a good man, Charlie;
I play by the rules.
This isn't me.
Sure it is. You
made up your mind
that you were gonna
figure out a way
to get Lyndsey a
nice birthday present.
The only part that isn't
you is that you succeeded.
I can't give these to Lyndsey--
they're tainted.
I have to sneak them back
into Judith's jewelry box.
Aw, you can't do that.
Why not?
Don't you watch TV?
Every time the crooks try
to put the stolen loot back,
it always goes horribly,
and hilariously, wrong.
I will just have
to take that chance.
Tomorrow I am going
back to Judith's,
and I'm gonna make this right.
Suit yourself.
(football game playing
at low volume)
I don't suppose you
want to come with me?
Maybe distract her while
I put the earrings back?
Yeah, that sounds
like a great plan.
What could go wrong?
Okay, I'll
do it myself.
Don't call me
for bail money.
Why not? You were gonna
give me money to buy a present.
You're not even planning
to get away with it?
Well, of course I am.
I was always planning to become
an astronaut and a cowboy.
♪ Men... ♪
Hey, baby.
(chuckles): Hey!
How was shopping?
Oh, we had a great time.
Yeah, it was a blast.
Look-- I got the same watch
Johnny Depp has.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, hold on.
You-you bought him all this?
Well, he was
so helpful.
Here you go, handsome.
Oh, by they way, you
got a parking ticket.
Damn it, Courtney,
I don't want you
buying stuff for that
clown on my credit card.
Why not? You
buy me stuff.
There's a difference.
What's that?
Well, you're having
sex with me,
and he's... well,
he's just screwing me.
(Jake chuckles evilly)
♪ Men... ♪
You okay, honey?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm-I'm just
a little tired.
Oh, of course you are.
You've been working so hard.
Mm-hmm.
I got a little
something for you.
Oh, Lyndsey, not tonight--
I'm dead from the waist down.
Silly! Not that.
This.
Oh. What is it?
Open it and see.
"A day of pampering
at the Beverly Glen Spa"?
You can get a massage,
scalp treatment, facial,
mani-pedi, anything you want.
What's the occasion?
You're my man--
you deserve it.
Oh, boy.
What's the matter?
Well, your birthday's
on Saturday.
Alan... I told you,
I don't expect
anything fancy or expensive.
I know you don't.
(laughs softly)
Which is why I
got you these!
(gasps)
You shouldn't have!
Tell me about it.
(nervous chuckle)
They must have
cost a fortune!
(laughs) Oh, not really.
I stole 'em.
(both laughing)
♪ Men... ♪
Oh. To my
birthday girl.
Thank you, sweetie.
How do they look? Almost as beautiful
as the woman who's wearing them.
Oh, Alan
(laughs)
Hey, hey, hey.
Judith. Judith, Herb.
(laughs)
Um, what a surprise.
What brings you here?
It's our, uh, weekly
in-lieu-of-sex dinner.
Herb!
Oopsy.
Hi, Lyndsey.
How have you been?
Good, thanks.
Uh, how about you?
Fine.
Alan, what is
wrong with you?
Oh, nothing.
I'm, uh, I'm just...
here with my girlfriend
having a little, uh,
a little birthday
celebration, you know.
What are
you doing?!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I just, I love it
when your hair is down--
it's so sexy. You know?
He's right, it is.
Would you like to
join us for a drink?
Great idea!
Uh, so, Lyndsey,
uh, happy birthday.
Thank you.
Did you get anything special?
LYNDSEY:
Well, as a matter of fact...
All right, I just have
to say something here!
You-you whine
and moan about
not having enough money
to buy decent clothes
for our son, and yet...
somehow there's enough
for you go out and have a...
a big fancy dinner!
What?
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
are you suddenly
hard of hearing?
Or are you just...
allergic to the truth?!
Oh, hey, hold on...
No, no, no, no!
This needs to be said!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
Shame! Shame, shame...
Shame.
Come on, Herb.
He's crazy.
Happy birthday,
Lyndsey.
I love the earrings.
JUDITH: Herb!
Coming.
Can you believe
I was married to that bitch?
♪ Men... ♪
(football game playing
at low volume)
- Hey.
Where have you been?
Oh, I was, uh, dropping
Jake off at his mother's.
How are you handling your guilt?
Oh, you mean
about the earrings?
Well, interesting thing.
It's much easier
the second time.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==